(Satori Shun) Let's go on a date ➡
With a partner
To deepen friendship.
(Hattori Maika)
Huh? Oh, ah, a bit...
Seat belt.
It's tasty.
good.
Huh?
(Mashima)
It's become a huge development.
(Narimitsu) You, right?
I sent that email. ➡
Are you planning on revenge?
Hey, answer it!
You don't need this company.
And in the future
I won't let her get close to him either.
I did this for revenge.
(Akiyama) Who is that?
♬〜
To Hattori Maika.
The president has been in the past ➡
Hattori Maika and
Is there any fate?
Her person is
It seems he doesn't remember the CEO though.
Of course I don't remember.
You know me from the old days, right?
Ah...
Your last name and title ➡
Appearance too...➡
Because everything has changed.
♬〜
(Buzzing)
(Narration) <Only good grades
I was the only one that I had had ➡
School hierarchy
He was in the lowest position
♬〜
<With a mother working at a snack bar
We lived together but...
(Photons, recollection)
｟Eat something just right and
♬〜
<Just at school or at home ➡
Make sure you keep your breathing
I was alive
｟Don! ｠
(Male student) ｟Ahhh
I couldn't see it. Sorry sorry ｠
(Male student)｟Really
I fell over. Haha
(Boys)
｟That's uncool. Be careful ｠
(Male student) Let's go ｠
｟Kagaya-kun. Are you okay? ｠
<Hatsutori Maika, who was her classmate,
He spoke to me >
｟That's terrible.
I bumped into it, it's over there
｟It's good Hattori-san｠
｟Even if you're involved with me
There's no benefit
｟It has nothing to do with profit or loss
｟This situation
It's harder to ignore it
♬〜
｟Yosho｠
｟Wow
You're reading a difficult book
｟I'm just novels
⦅yes⦆
｟Novel... do you like it? ｠
⦅Yeah⦆
｟Ah｠
｟Hand injured
♬〜
⦅yes. Use this
⦅No, it's fine⦆
⦅No good, it's bloody⦆
⦅yes⦆
⦅thank you…⦆
(Kozue)⦅Maika What are you doing? ⦆
(Akane)⦅I'm going home⦆
⦅Ah yes⦆
｟Kagaya-kun See you tomorrow｠
♬〜
I knew it was high hopes
<Anyway
I fell in love >
♬〜
⦅yeah? what? this⦆
｟I've read recently
Because it was the most interesting
｟Hattori Reading books
It seems like I love it...｠
⦅thank you! Read it ｠
⦅Yeah⦆
♬〜
⦅yes⦆
｟The ending of this book was amazing, isn't it?
｟I never expected it at all｠
｟Make this person's debut
Did you read it? ｠
｟Uh, I haven't read it yet
｟Shall I lend it next time?
I think I definitely like it
｟Yes, I want to read it! ｠
｟I'll take it with me tomorrow
⦅thank you⦆
｟Ehhh I'm looking forward to it｠
There is also a common hobby of reading.
We became friends...➡
I felt like we had a connection.
♬〜
So I had a stupid dream.
｟Hattori is... I love it｠
⦅Eh? ⦆
⦅⚞ (students) hahaha⦆
♬〜
｟Tomorrow at 5am➡
I'll be waiting in the usual park
｟Kagaya-kun...｠
｟I want you to hear a reply｠
♬〜
｟I understand｠
｟📱(Ringtone)｠
｟📱(Incoming email/manner mode)｠
♬〜
In the end she was the same
< Just like with other classmates ➡
He was looking down on me >
♬〜
After that
His mother was soon remarried.
I'm going to transfer school
That's how it went with her.
But ➡
Hattori Maika really becomes the president
Have you not noticed it?
ah.
My last name has also changed
I can't believe the president of my company
That introvert
You never thought of it.
President Satori remarried his mother
The best reason is ➡
With the excellent Shun as his successor ➡
Because I wanted to welcome you
I'm listening.
ah.
｟⚟Konkonkon(Knokku)｠
I'm an academically excellent person
I welcomed him as my son.
(Kenichi) ｟You came so well ｠
< So that day ➡
I'm
I vowed to meet my father-in-law's expectations.
⦅thank you⦆
(Kenichi)⦅Yes⦆
♬〜
<Strive to study to become a successor ➡
By the time I went to university
I'm already
It's no longer the old me
♬〜
<Assumed as president ➡
It has become a winner that the public calls it>
♬〜
Meet her again ➡
The humiliation I had forgotten was revived.
♬〜
To break the engagement decided by your parents
Because I needed to throw away pieces.
I'm Hattori Maika ➡
He approached him to become a fake lover.
The hurtful past
I want to repaint...➡
Is that what you mean?
♬〜
Anyway, people are
He judges people only by their appearance and title.
♬〜
The same goes for Hattori Maika.
Huh?
(Mashima) What's wrong?
Ah, no...
My vision is a bit blurry.
(Mashima) Are you sleeping properly? ➡
Overtime continues
Are you tired? ➡
What, isn't it?
Ah... it's okay.
That's all that first...
(Mashima) That's fine ➡
Go to the doctor's office soon! ➡
Come on, hurry up.
yes….
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha... ha...
Ha ha ha...
Maika!
president.
It's incredibly hot.
(Akiyama) Immediately went to the hospital.
No, I'll carry it.
♬〜
Ping Pong (Eleveter arrival sound)
Please do all the afternoon plans.
(Akiyama) President.
♬〜
Have you woke up?
Here...
Ah, my apartment.
I was surprised because I suddenly fell over.
Huh? Ah, that's it...
Ah, work, is it okay?
it's okay.
What's more, how's it?
Ahhh ➡
already
It feels completely back to normal.
good. The IV drip worked.
Yeah.
It looks like the fever has subsided.
Ah
Sorry... if it's me...
Should I eat something, right?
I made porridge but...
Huh?
♬〜
yes.
Ah, thank you very much.
I'll enjoy having this.
Yeah.
♬〜
delicious.
good.
I can feel the kindness of Shun.
I am a happy person.
♬〜
exaggerated.
lend me.
Huh?
♬〜
yes.
Huh? Ah, no no, that's not it...
That's fine. Open your mouth.
yes.
I can't do it!
Ah... I'm sorry
I'm familiar with it.
♬〜
why?
They're lovers...
I could touch it more.
This... Even if I say my lover
It's fake ➡
You have to draw a proper line.
If so...
♬〜
To a real lover
Isn't it good to be?
Huh?
Don't joke.
Me and Shun
It's not worth it.
♬〜
What should I do...
How can you look at me?
Shun?
♬〜
sorry.
(Voice in the heart) <Yesterday's Shun ➡
What did it mean? ≫
｟How can you look at me? ｠
<Was he serious?
Was it a joke...?
⚞Try and work...(Footsteps)
(Mashima) What? Is it okay already?
Ah yes
It's completely restored to normal now.
(Mashima) Ahhhh, that's good.
Or rather, yesterday I went to the hospital to the president
Is it true that you brought it to me?
Ah
Um... I'm gonna be so excited ➡
I don't remember very well though.
(Mashima) Yes, yes.
It seems you were kind.
(Mashima) Really?
Is there any two of you?
Ah, no, nothing.
That's right. ➡
But the president is for everyone
He's a prince character.
If I get a fever too
Maybe I'll be able to hold you in a princess.
Ahh.
Ping Pong
Vienna Batan (Eleveter's door sound)
<That's right. It's not serious≫
<<I'm just
For the president to break the engagement ➡
Because he's a fake lover≫
Ping Pong
♬〜
<<What?
Even if he's a false lover...≫
♬〜
<<Several times so far
He saved me from a crisis≫
♬〜
｟Ah...｠
｟ Become a fake lover with me ➡
Revenge on the two... No ➡
Would you like to look back at the two of you? ｠
｟Are you planning to revenge?
Hey, answer it! ｠
♬〜
｟Don't get in the way｠
<<Do this now
You can usually come to work ➡
Thanks to Shun-san≫
｟I'm sorry for making you feel so bad｠
｟Maika! ｠
⦅president⦆
⦅It's so hot⦆
(Akiyama)⦅ Immediately to the hospital⦆
｟No, I'll carry it
♬〜
(Akiyama) I had planned it yesterday afternoon
Please go to a representative to inspect the factory.
Dinner with Jones while he was visiting Japan
It was delayed to Friday.
ah. Sorry.
If I don't do that much
Because I can't make her get serious.
(Akiyama) Is that all?
What does it mean?
Actually, my feelings for Hattori Maika ➡
Unconsciously
Isn't it dragging you?
Idiot.
⚞Kong Kong
(Akiyama) Yes.
⚟ (female secretary) Excuse me.
The CEO is a customer.
Please pass it through.
⚞Gacha (door sound)
(Mitsuko) Shun It's been a while.
Mom. Why?
(Photons)
No matter how many times I call, I won't answer.
There's an important story.
no….
(Akiyama)Excuse me.
(Photon) Sunday
A dinner party with Kotone's family.
I've said it many times but
I'm not going.
That's what
There's no way it'll be recognized. ➡
This marriage
What does it mean?
You know, right?
Mom ➡
I've been
Everything, just as your mother said ➡
I've chosen my life.
But beyond this
I want to choose my own life.
What is your will
I haven't heard it. ➡
Thanks to who
Do you think you could sit in this chair?
♬〜
more
Be aware of the president. ➡
What should you prioritize for the company?
If you think about it calmly, you'll understand.
♬〜
⚟(photon) Please
Don't be rude to the other party.
⚟I understand.
♬〜
(Kotone) Shun-san, you're late.
(Photon) Sorry. ➡
"Please don't be rude."
I told you that...
(Kotone's father)
He was just appointed president.
Quite a flexible time
It probably won't work. ➡
Let's wait a little longer.
(Photon) Sorry. ➡
Um... call again.
Swoo (the sound of the brush)
Sorry for the delay.
(Kotone) Shun!
(Photon)
Everyone has been waiting for you. ➡
what happened? Sit quickly.
What I didn't talk about this time
Could you please do this?
(Mitsuko) Shun.
To me
There are other women who have decided on their minds.
(Photon) What are you going to say?
Excuse me.
(Mitsuko) Wait Shun!
⚟Gatcha
♬〜
Slap! (The sound of a drink)
Ah.
♬〜
Ah! Ah, sorry! ➡
OK?
Ah, it's okay.
Um... are you okay with that?
♬〜
that….
(Piano sound)
Ah... Ah, yes it's fine.
♬〜
With Shun
I'm dating you.
you
He's just one who's convenient for you.
Shun stopped listening to what he said
Is it your fault?
From past ties
To be released ➡
I think they're leaving here.
Let's break down the fake love relationship today.